Today we are going to celebrate
Dziś świętujemy
the Puja of Gauri.
Pudźę Shri Gauri.
She came on this earth
Przyszła Ona na ziemię
many-a-times to kill the people
wielokrotnie aby zniszczyć ludzi,
who were doing wrong things,
którzy robili złe rzeczy,
who were trying to kill good people.
którzy próbowali zabić dobrych ludzi.
She has done Her level to do that,
Zrobiła wszystko co było w jej mocy aby to osiągnąć,
and today we are celebrating Her birthday.
i dzisiaj świętujemy Jej urodziny.
You all know so much about it
Wszyscy wiecie bardzo dużo o tym,
that I need not tell you,
więc nie ma potrzeby powtarzać się,
but what you have to know is that
ale musicie wiedzieć, że
She came on this earth to save you
Ona przyszła na tę ziemię, aby uratować was
from all kinds of troubles.
od wszelkich problemów.
For Her you were important, very important,
Dla Niej byliście ważni, bardzo ważni,
because you were doing Devi Puja.
ponieważ wykonywaliście Pudźę do Dewi.
And so we are celebrating today this Devi Puja,
I właśnie dziś świętujemy Pudźę Dewi,
with all our heart,
całym waszym sercem.
because whatever ill people did to you,
Ponieważ cokolwiek źli ludzie wam zrobili,
She came to destroy them.
Ona przyszła aby ich zniszczyć.
So today is a very great day for you to thank Her,
A więc to jest wspaniały dzień abyście Jej podziękowali;
thank Her for Her protection and
podziękowali Jej za ochronę
for Her understanding
i za to, że rozumie
as to what you have been tortured for.
jak bardzo byliście torturowani.
I'm happy you are all here to celebrate Her birthday,
Jestem szczęśliwa, że jesteście tu aby świętować Jej urodziny,
and to be surrendered to Her
i aby oddać się Jej tak,
so that She can always,
aby mogła zawsze,
always protect you
zawsze was chronić
and give you Her blessings.
i dawać wam błogosławieństwa.
So may God bless you all,
A więc niech Bóg was wszystkich błogosławi,
your children,
wasze dzieci,
your families,
wasze rodziny,
and that you bring great joy and protection.
abyście osiągnęli ogromną radość i ochronę.
It's very kind of you to have come today, so far away.
To bardzo miłe z waszej strony, że przybyliście dziś z tak daleka.
I'm very happy to see you.
Jestem bardzo szczęśliwa, że was widzę.
Moreover, you have got tomorrow also
Co więcej, mamy także jutrzejszy dzień
that you can celebrate.
aby świętować.
Today we are not going to have any questions and solutions;
Dzisiaj nie będzie żadnych pytań i odpowiedzi,
we are just going to worship the Goddess, that's all,
po prostu będziemy czcić Boginię, to wszystko
and request Her to protect us
i poprosimy Ją aby nas chroniła
from all kinds of problems that are facing us.
przed wszystkimi problemami z którymi się mierzymy.
Thank you very much.
Bardzo wam dziękuję.